Guide to the New-York Historical Society Postcard Collection [graphic] circa 1898-1965 (bulk, 1900-1950) PR 54
New-York Historical Society
- Series II. Geographic Locations | New York, circa 1898-1965 (bulk, 1900-1950); 27.89 Linear feet (in 51.5 boxes)
  - Subseries II.B. New York City, circa 1898-1965 (bulk, 1900-1950); 13 Linear feet (in 24 boxes)
    - Manhattan | Churches & Synagogues | Synagogues (Box 47)
      Congregation Beth El (945 Fifth Avenue)
      Congregation Emanu-El (56 Chrystie Street, 519 Fifth Avenue, and 1 East 65th)
    - Manhattan | Churches & Synagogues | Souvenir Folders & Sets (Box 96-D)
      St. Francis of Assisi (Roman Catholic, 135 West 31st) (1)
      St. John the Divine (Episcopal, 1047 Amsterdam Avenue) (3)
      Riverside Church (American Baptist / United Church of Christ, 490 Riverside Drive) (1; artwork)
    - Manhattan | Clubs & Organizations (Box 47)
      Seaman's Institute
      YMCA & YWCA
    - Manhattan | Courts (Box 47)
    - Manhattan | Department Stores, Shops (Box 47)
    - Manhattan | Exchanges (Box 47)
    - Manhattan | Firefighting (includes Fire Boats) (Box 47)
    - Manhattan | Homes & Asylums (Box 47)
    - Manhattan | Hospitals (Box 48)
    - Manhattan | Hotels (A) (Box 48)
      Aberdeen
      Alamac
      Albert
      Alden
      Allerton House
      Ambassador
      Americana
      Ansonia
      Astor
      Astor House
    - Manhattan | Hotels (B) (Box 48)
      Barbizon-Plaza
      Bedford
      Belleclaire
      Belmont
      Belmont Plaza
      Berkley
      Berkshire
      Biltmore
      Breslin
      Bretton Hall
      Brevoort
      Bristol
      Broadway Central
    - Manhattan | Hotels (C) (Box 48)
      Carteret
      Chatham
      Chelsea
      Chesterfield
      Claridge
      Clendening
      Colonial
      Commodore
      Commonwealth
      Concourse Plaza
      Cosmopolitan
      Croydon
    - Manhattan | Hotels (D) (Box 48)
      Dauphin
      Delmonico
      Dixie
      Duane
    - Manhattan | Hotels (E) (Box 48)
      East End
      Earle
      Edison
      Elysee
      Emerson
      Empire
      Endicott
      Essex House
      Everett House
    - Manhattan | Hotels (F) (Box 48)
      Fifth Avenue (old)
      Fifth Avenue (new)
      Flanders
      Florence House
      Forrest
    - Manhattan | Hotels (G) (Box 48)
      George Washington
      Gilsey House
      Gotham
      Governor Clinton
      Grand Union
      Great Northern
      Gregorian
    - Manhattan | Hotels (H) (Box 48)
      Henry Hudson
      Herald Square
      Hermitage
      Hilton
      Hoffman House
      Holland House
      Holley
      Howard Johnson's
    - Manhattan | Hotels (I) (Box 48)
      Imperial / Robert Stafford
      International
      Irving
    - Manhattan | Hotels (J) (Box 48)
      Jermyn
      Joe Schmitt's
    - Manhattan | Hotels (K) (Box 48)
      Kimberly
      King Edward
      King's Crown
      Knickerbocker (old)
      Knickerbocker (new)
    - Manhattan | Hotels (L) (Box 48)
      Lafayette
      Langham
      La Salle
      Latham
      Le Marquis
      Leonori
      Libby's Hotel and Baths, Delancey Street
      Longacre
    - Manhattan | Hotels (Mc) (Box 49)
      McAlpin
    - Manhattan | Hotels (M) (Box 49)
      Madison Square
      Majestic (old)
      Manger
      Manhattan
      Manhattan Square
      Marie Antoinette
      Markwell
      Marlborough
      Marlton
      Marseilles
      Martha Washington
      Martinique
      Metropole
      Midston House
      Murray Hill
    - Manhattan | Hotels (N) (Box 49)
      Navarre
      New Grand
      New Weston
      New Yorker
      New York Hilton
      Netherland and Savoy
    - Manhattan | Hotels (O) (Box 49)
      Oliver Cromwell
      One Fifth Avenue
      Orleans
    - Manhattan | Hotels (P) (Box 49)
      Paramount
      Park Avenue
      Park Central
      Park Crescent
      Park Lane
      Park Plaza
      Park-Sheraton
      Pennsylvania
      Peter Stuyvesant
      Piccadilly
      Pickwick Arms
      Pierre
      Plaza
      Prince George
    - Manhattan | Hotels (R) (Box 49)
      Ritz
      Ritz-Carlton
      Riverside Plaza
      Roosevelt
      Royalton
      Russell
      Rutledge
    - Manhattan | Hotels (S) (Box 49)
      St. Andrew
      St. Denis
      St. James
      St. Moritz
      St. Regis
      Salisbury
      San Rafael
      San Remo (old)
      Savoy
      Savoy Plaza
      Seville
      Seymour
      Shelton
      Sherman Square
      Sheraton
      Sheraton-Astor
      Sherry-Netherland
      Skyline Motor Inn
      Stattler
      Stratford
      Sulgrave
      Summit
    - Manhattan | Hotels (T) (Box 49)
      Taft
      Ten Eyck
      Theresa
      Times Square
      Town House
    - Manhattan | Hotels (V) (Box 49)
      Vanderbilt
      Victoria (old)
      Victoria (new)
      Vista
    - Manhattan | Hotels (W) (Box 49)
      Waldorf-Astoria (old)
      Waldorf-Astoria (new)
      Wallick
      Wellington
      Westbury
      West Shore
      White
      Willard
      Wolcott
      Woodward
    - Manhattan | Insurance Buildings (Box 49)
      Metropolitan Life Insurance
    - Manhattan | Libraries (Box 50)
      New York Public Library
    - Manhattan | Markets (Box 50)
    - Manhattan | Monuments (Box 50)
      Dewey Arch
      Grant's Tomb
      Lincoln Monument
      Maine Monument
      Sigel, Franz Monument
      Soldiers' and Sailors' Monument
      Victory Arch
      Washington Arch
    - Manhattan | Museums (Box 50-51)
      American Museum of Natural History
      Hispanic Society of America
      Kosciuzko Foundation House
      Metropolitan Museum of Art
      Metropolitan Museum of Art | Cloisters
      New-York Historical Society
    - Manhattan | Neighborhoods (Box 51)
      Chinatown
      Financial District
      Greenwich Village
      Harlem
      Lower East Side
      Tenderloin
      Washington Heights
    - Manhattan | Parks, Squares, and Circles (Box 51)
      Parks A-Z
      Squares A-Z
      Battery Park
      Bowling Green
      Bryant Park
    - Manhattan | Parks, Squares, and Circles (continued) (Box 52)
      Central Park
      Activities
      Band Stand
      Belvedere
      Bethesda Fountain
      Boat House
      Mall
      Obelisk
      Observatory
      Paths, Drives, etc.
      Terraces
      Zoo
    - Manhattan | Parks, Squares, and Circles (continued) (Box 52-53)
      Chatham Square
      City Hall Park
      Columbus Circle
      Cooper Square
      Gramercy Park
      Longacre Square
      Morningside Park
      Mount Morris Park
      Mulberry Bend Park
      Riverside Park
      Union Square
      Verdi Square
      Washington Square
    - Manhattan | Police Stations & Prisons (Box 53)
    - Manhattan | Post Offices (Box 53)
      Old Post Office (City Hall)
      New Post Office (8th Avenue)
    - Manhattan | Residences (Box 53)
      Jumel Mansion
      Theodore Roosevelt Birthplace
    - Manhattan | Restaurants (A) (Box 54)
      Anderson's Campus
      Arrowhead Inn, Ben Riley's
      Artist and Writer's
      Attilio's
      Automat (830 Broadway)
    - Manhattan | Restaurants (B) (Box 54)
      Balkan Armenian
      Bal Tabarin
      Barbetta
      Beefburger Hall
      Bird in Hand
      Blossom
      Blue Heron
      Blue Ribbon
      Bonat's Cafe
      Boulevard de Paris
      Brass Rail
      Steve Brodie on the Bowery
    - Manhattan | Restaurants (C) (Box 54)
      Café des Artistes
      Café des Beaux-Arts
      Café Elysee
      Café Geiger
      Café Lafayette
      Café Louis XIV
      Café Madison
      Café Martin
      Café Raub
      Café Vaterland
      Campfire Inn
      Captain's Table
      Casino Russe
      Castle Cave
      Castleholm
      Cavanagh's
      Chalet Suisse
      Champs Elysees
      Chandler's
      Chardas
      Charles French
      Charleston Garden (in B. Altman & Co.)
      Chez Maurice
      Childs
      Chin Lee American and Chinese
      China Garden
      Chinatown Charlie
      Chinese Tuxedo
      Churchill's (Broadway & 49th Street)
      Churchill's (42nd Street & Park Avenue)
      Colaizzi's Table d'Hote
      Commerce Inn
      Constantinople
      Conte's
      Copacabana
      Cortile
      Court
      Croton Cottage
      Cup 'n Saucer Cottage
      Claremont Inn
    - Manhattan | Restaurants (D) (Box 54)
      Delmonico's
      De Luxe
      Jack Dempsey's Broadway Restaurant
      H.T. Dewey & Sons
      Divan Parisien
    - Manhattan | Restaurants (E) (Box 54)
      Eat Shoppe
      82 Club Revue
      86th St. Brauhaus
      Eldorado Rotisserie
      Empire Diner
    - Manhattan | Restaurants (F) (Box 54)
      Far East Restaurant
      Faust Café and Restaurant
      Fifth Avenue Hotel Restaurant
      Fifth Avenue Tavern
      Firenze
      Flea Market Cafe-Restaurant (131 Avenue A)
      Fleischmann's Vienna Restaurant
      "400" Restaurant
      Flying Trapeze
      Folies Bergére Ivan Frank and his Bavarian Entertainers
      Francais
      Fraunces Tavern
    - Manhattan | Restaurants (G) (Box 54)
      Gallagher's Steak House
      Garden Cafeteria
      Garden Restaurant
      Geigers Konditorei und Kaffee
      German American Rathskeller
      Gertner's
      Gilhuly Bros.
      Gilmore's Restaurant
      Gilmore's Steakhouse
      Giolito Bros. Cedar Garden
      Giolito Venetian Garden
      Grand Central Terminal Restaurant / Oyster Bar
      Janssen Graybar
      Greenwich Village Inn
      Grill Room, Hotel McAlpin
      Gus-andy's
    - Manhattan | Restaurants (H) (Box 54)
      Hapsburg House
      Havana Madrid
      Headquarters Restaurant
      Thomas Healy's
      Hector's
      Hickory House
      Hof-bräu Haus
      Horn & Hardart Automat
      Huber's
    - Manhattan | Restaurants (I) (Box 54)
      Iceland Restaurant
      Idle Hour
      Indian Grill Room, Hotel Astor
    - Manhattan | Restaurants (J) (Box 54)
      Jardin Royal
      Joe King's Fraternity House
      Joe King's Rathskeller
      Jumble Shop
    - Manhattan | Restaurants (K) (Box 54)
      Kalil's Park Place Restaurant
      Keen's English Chop House
      Kellogg's Cafeteria
      King's
      Kleine Konditorei
      Knickerbocker Grill Chinese and American Restaurant
    - Manhattan | Restaurants (L) (Box 54)
      La Fourchette
      L'Armorique
      Larre's Restaurant and Cafe
      Le Café Arnold
      Le Café Chambord
      Le Chambertin
      Le Chanteclair
      Lee's
      Leon and Eddie's
      Le Parisienne Rotisserie
      Les Pyrenees
      Lindy's
      Lion D'Or Table D'Hote
      Lion's Rock
      Little Hungary
      Lobster
      Chas. S Low
      Lüchow's
      Lum Fong
    - Manhattan | Restaurants (Mc) (Box 54)
      Alice McCollister Restaurant
      McGown's Pass Tavern
      McGinnis' of Sheepshead Bay
    - Manhattan | Restaurants (M) (Box 54)
      Madison Cottage
      Majors Cabin Grill
      Mandy's Planked Steak House
      Manny Wolf's Chop House
      Mario's Villa d'Este
      Marta Cabaret
      Mercura
      Mermaid Room
      Mertin's
      Miyako
      Mont D'or Restaurant
      Mouquin's
      Murray's
    - Manhattan | Restaurants (N) (Box 54)
      Niemeyer's
    - Manhattan | Restaurants (O) (Box 54)
      Oh-Ho-So
      Old Brew House
      Old China
      Olde Chop House
      Olde Dutch Tavern
      One if By Land, Two if By Sea
    - Manhattan | Restaurants (P) (Box 54)
      Pacific Chinese Restaurant
      Paddy's Clam House
      Parisien
      Paul & Jimmy's
      Peck's Downtown Table D'Hote
      Pekin
      Penguin Restaurant
      Penthouse
      Pepper Pot
      Peter's Backyard
      Pete's Tavern
      Pierre's
      Pirate's Den
      Platzl
      Pontin's
      Port Arthur
      Primavera
      Promenade Cafe (Rockefeller Center)
    - Manhattan | Restaurants (R) (Box 54)
      Rector's
      Red Coach Grill
      Reisenweber's
      Republic
      Reuben's
      Rheinland Cabaret and Restaurant
      Riggs'
      Rincon Argentino
      Rosoff's
      Roth's
      Ruby Foo's
      Ruskay's
      Russian Bear
      Russian Kretchma
      Russian Inn
      Russian Tea Room
    - Manhattan | Restaurants (S) (Box 54)
      St. George
      Saddle Bar
      Saw Dust Trail
      Sea Cove
      Sea Fare
      Schrafft's
      Shanley's
      Lou G. Siegel
      Sloppy Louie's
      Steak Casino
      Steak Joint
      Still's
      Stockholm
      Strand Roof Garden
      Sun Luck (143 West 49th & 75 East 55th)
      Swedish Rathskeller
      Sweets
      Swing Rendezvous
      Swiss Cafe
      Subway Tavern
    - Manhattan | Restaurants (T) (Box 54)
      Tally-Ho
      Tavern-on-the-Green
      Terrace
      Toffenetti
      Tokay
      Tokio
      Town and Country
      "21"
      Trader Vic's
      Troger's
    - Manhattan | Restaurants (U) (Box 54)
      Unter Den Linden
    - Manhattan | Restaurants (V) (Box 54)
      Village Barn
      Voll's Alhambra Garden
    - Manhattan | Restaurants (W) (Box 54)
      Wallick's
      Whyte's
      Wivel
      Woolworth Rathskeller
    - Manhattan | Restaurants (Y) (Box 54)
      Yorkville Casino
    - Manhattan | Restaurants (Z) (Box 54)
      Zimmerman's Hungaria
      Zucca's Italian Garden
    - Manhattan | Schools & Colleges (Box 55-A)
      College of the City of New York
      Columbia University, Miscellaneous
      Columbia University, Barnard College, Teacher's College
      General Theological Seminary
      New York University
      Normal College
      Washington Irving School
    - Manhattan | Skyline Views (Box 55-A & 55-B)
      Aerial
      From east (Brooklyn & Queens)
      From west (New Jersey & Hudson River)
      From ferries & water
      From islands
      from Governor's Island
      from Liberty Island
      from Staten Island
      From bridges
      From buildings
      from Empire State Building
      from Produce Exchange Building
      from Singer Building
      from Woolworth Building
      from World Building
      Lower Manhattan general
      Midtown Manhattan general
      Night views
    - Manhattan | Sports Facilities (Box 55-B)
      Madison Square Garden (various locations)
      Polo Grounds
    - Manhattan | Streets, numbered (Box 55-B)
      Below 20th
      20s
      30s
      40s
      60s
      60s-90s
      100s-200s
    - Manhattan | Streets, named (Box 55-B & 55-C)
      Bowery
      Broadway
      Chambers Street
      Harlem River Speedway/Drive
      Hester Street
      Nassau Street
      Park Row
      Riverside Drive
      Wall Street
    - Manhattan | Avenues, numbered (Box 55-C)
      First - Fourth Avenues
      Fifth Avenue
      Sixth Avenue
      Seventh Avenue
      Eighth Avenue
    - Manhattan | Avenues, named (Box 55-C)
    - Manhattan | Theaters & Entertainment Venues (Box 55-C)
      Theaters
      Hippodrome
      Radio City Music Hall
      Roxy Theater
      Theatrical Performances
      Opera Houses
      Recital Halls
      Roof Gardens
    - Manhattan | Transportation (Box 55-C & 56)
      Subways
      Stations & kiosks
      Tracks, tunnels
      Tracks, elevated
      PATH tubes & stations
      Terminals
      Brooklyn Bridge Terminal
      Grand Central Terminal
      Hudson Terminal
      Pennsylvania (Penn) Station
      Port Authority Bus Terminal
      Highways & Vehicular Tunnels
      East River Drive
      Henry Hudson Parkway
      Holland Tunnel
      Lincoln Tunnel
    - Manhattan | Utilities (Box 56)
    - Manhattan | Waterways (Box 56)
      Harbor views
      East River
      Harlem River
      Piers & docks
      Ferries, Boats, Ships
    - Manhattan | Oversize (Box 97 (folders 3-8))
    - Manhattan | Oversize (continued) (Oversize Flat File-D)
    - Brooklyn (Box 56)
      Brighton Beach
      Brooklyn Navy Yard
    - Brooklyn | Buildings (Box 56-57)
      Apartments
      Asylums
      Department Stores
      Factories, Warehouses
      Hotels, Inns & Restaurants
      Libraries & Museums Office Buildings
      Prisons
      Religious Institutions, etc.
      Baptist Churches
      Congregational Churches
      Convents
      Episcopal Churches
      Lutheran Churches
      Methodist Churches
      Presbyterian Churches
      Reformed Churches
      Roman Catholic Churches
      Miscellaneous Churches
      Synagogues
      Cemeteries
      Erasmus Hall High School
      Public Schools Nos. 1-147
      Packer Collegiate Institute
      Miscellaneous Schools
      Theatres & Miscellaneous
    - Brooklyn (continued) (Box 57-58)
      City Life
      Coney Island
      Dreamland
      Luna Park
      Steeplechase
      Manhattan Beach
      Markets, Yards, Exchanges, etc.
      Military
      Prospect Park
      Sports and Recreation
      Waterfront
    - Brooklyn | Souvenir Folders & Sets (Box 96-D)
      General (3)
      Coney Island (8)
      New York Aquarium (1)
    - Brooklyn | Oversize (Box 97 (folder 9))
    - Bronx (Box 58-59)
      Bronx Botanical Gardens
      Bronx River
      Fordham University
      Heine Monument
      Parkchester
      Pelham Bay Park
      Poe Cottage
      Public Schools
      Van Cortlandt Park
      Van Cortlandt Mansion
      Yankee Stadium
      Zoological Park
    - Queens (Box 59)
      Airports
      Astoria
      Broad Channel
      Corona
      Elmhurst
      Flushing
      Forest Hills
      Hollis
      Jackson Heights
      Jamaica
      Long Island City
      Richmond Hill
      Rockaways
    - Queens | Souvenir Folders & Sets (Box 96-D)
      Astoria & Long Island City
      John F. Kennedy International Airport
      Rockaway Beach
    - Staten Island (Box 60)
      Fort Wadsworth
      Sailors' Snug Harbor
- Series III. Geographic Locations | International, circa 1898-1965 (bulk, 1900-1950); 2.16 Linear feet (in 4 boxes)
  - Subseries III.A. Africa
    - Algeria (Box 86-A)
    - Egypt (Box 86-A)
    - Egypt | Oversize (Box 97 (folder 10))
    - Kenya (Box 86-A)
    - Morocco (Box 86-A)
    - South Africa (Box 86-A)
    - Tanzania (Box 86-A)
  - Subseries III.B. Caribbean
    - Bahamas (Box 86-A)
    - Barbados (Box 86-A)
    - Bermuda (Box 86-A)
    - Cuba (Box 86-A)
      Havana
    - Cuba | Souvenir Folders & Sets (Box 88)
      Havana (2)
    - Curacao (Box 86-A)
    - Dominican Republic and Haiti (Box 86-A)
    - Guadaloupe (Box 86-A)
    - Jamaica (Box 86-A)
    - Martinique (Box 86-A)
    - Puerto Rico (Box 86-A)
    - Puerto Rico | Souvenir Folders & Sets (Box 88)
    - St. Thomas (Box 86-A)
    - Trinidad (Box 86-A)
    - Virgin Islands (Box 86-A)
    - West Indies (Box 86-A)
  - Subseries III.C. Europe
    - Austria (Box 86-A)
    - Austria | Oversize (Box 97 (folder 10))
    - Belgium (Box 86-A)
    - Bosnia and Herzegovina (Box 86-A)
    - Croatia (Box 86-A)
    - Denmark (Box 86-A)
    - England (Box 86-A)
    - England | Oversize (Box 97 (folder 10))
    - France (Box 86-B)
    - France | Oversize (Box 97 (folder 10))
    - Germany (Box 86-B)
    - Germany | Oversize (Box 97 (folder 10))
    - Gibraltar (Box 86-B)
    - Greece (Box 86-B)
    - Iceland (Box 86-B)
    - Ireland (Box 86-B)
    - Italy (Box 86-B)
    - Italy | Oversize (Box 97 (folder 10))
    - Liechtenstein (Box 86-B)
    - Malta (Box 86-B)
    - Monaco (Box 86-B)
    - Netherlands (Box 86-B)
    - Netherlands | Oversize (Box 97 (folder 10))
    - Norway (Box 86-B)
    - Portugal (Box 86-B)
    - Russia (Box 86-B)
    - Scotland (Box 86-B)
    - Scotland | Oversize (Box 97 (folder 10))
    - Spain (Box 86-B)
    - Sweden (Box 86-B)
    - Switzerland (Box 86-B)
    - Switzerland | Souvenir Folders & Sets (Box 88)
      Pilatus
  - Subseries III.D. Middle East
    - Israel (Box 86-B)
    - Israel | Souvenir Folders & Sets (Box 88)
      Masada
    - Israel | Oversize (Box 97 (folder 10))
    - Lebanon (Box 86-B)
  - Subseries III.E. North and Central America
    - Canada (Box 86-B)
      Alberta
      Banff
      Jasper National Park
      Lake Louise
      Moraine Lake
      British Columbia
      Field
      Glacier
      Vancouver
      Victoria
      Manitoba
      Fredericton
      St. John
      Newfoundland
    - Canada (continued) (Box 87)
      Nova Scotia
      Annapolis Royal
      Cape Breton Island | General
      Cape Breton Island | Louisburg
      Digby
      Halifax
      Yarmouth
      Ontario
      Brantford
      Ottawa
      Queenston
      Toronto
      Prince Edward Island
      Quebec A-Z
      Gaspe
      Lake Memphremagog
      Montmorency
      Montreal | Buildings
      Montreal | Chateau de Ramezay
      Montreal | Churches
      Montreal | Harbor and Waterways
      Montreal | Hotels
      Montreal | Mont Royal
      Montreal | Streets, Squares and Markets
      Montreal | Views and Monuments
      Montreal | General
      Murray Bay
      Quebec City | Buildings
      Quebec City | Hotels and Restaurants
      Quebec City | Monuments
      Quebec City | Plains of Abraham
      Quebec City | Streets, Squares, Gates, Markets
      Quebec City | Views
      Quebec City | General
    - Canada (continued) (Box 88)
      Quebec
      Saquenay River
      Saint Anne de Beaupré
      Tadoussac
      Saskatchewan
      Canadian Rockies
      Canada General
    - Canada | Souvenir Folders & Sets (Box 88)
      Fort Edmonton (1)
      Maligne Canyon
      Banff / Lake Louise
      Saint John (2)
      Cape Breton Island
      Port Royal Habitation
      Canadian National Exhibition, Toronto (2)
      Montreal
      Quebec City
    - Canada | Miniature (Box 98)
      Quebec and Ste. Anne de Beaupre
    - Guatemala (Box 88)
    - Mexico (Box 88)
    - Panama (Box 88)
    - Panama | Souvenir Folders & Sets (Box 88)
    - Panama Canal Zone (Box 88)
  - Subseries III.F. Pacific
    - Japan (Box 88)
    - Philippines (Box 88)
  - Subseries III.G. South America
    - Argentina (Box 88)
    - Brazil (Box 88)
    - Brazil | Oversize (Box 97 (folder 10))
    - Colombia (Box 88)
    - Uruguay (Box 88)
    - Venezuela (Box 88)
  - Subseries III.H. South Asia
    - India (Box 88)
    - Indonesia (Box 88)
    - Pakistan (Box 88)
- Series IV. Subjects, circa 1898-1965 (bulk, 1900-1950); 3.79 Linear feet (in 7 boxes)
  Cards are filed alphabetically by subject.
  - Activities & Occupations (Box 89)
  - Advertising (Box 89)
    Theatrical Advertising
  - American Art (Box 89)
  - American History (Box 89)
    1492-1769
    1770-1783
    1784-1850
    1851-1897
    1898-1910
    1911-1919
    1920-1950
    1951-present
    Patriotic – Flags, seals, etc.
  - Comic (Box 89)
  - Correspondence (Box 99)
    Postcards mailed to individuals or families, kept together for their informational content.
    BIRCH family (Carthage, Ohio) [17 cards], 1905-1909
    BRADLEY family (Ossining, New York) [6 cards], 1907-1924
    Includes one card from Elizaeth Bradley, of Ossining, addressed to Edith A. Ferguson, of Eldred, Sullivan County, New York.
    HEGNER family (Valley Stream, New York) [16 cards], 1955-1961
    A number of cards are addressed in care of "Alden Delicatessen." The Hegners are possible relatives of the Johnson and Mulholland families, which see.
    HYATT family (Milford, Connecticut) [29 cards], 1905-1912
    JOHNSON family ([South?] Ozone Park, New York) [8 cards], 1949-1957
    The Johnsons are possible relatives of the Hegner and Mulholland families, which see.
    LONG family (Framingham, Ashland, and Braintree, Massachusetts) [6 cards], 1905-1946
    MC ARTHUR family (Carthage and Cincinnati, Ohio) [3 cards], 1905-1912
    MIXELL family (Stroudsburg, Pennsylvania) [2 cards], 1913, undated
    MULHOLLAND family (Richmond Hill and [South?] Ozone Park, New York) [16 cards], 1941-1960
    The Mulhollands are possible relatives of the Hegner and Johnson families, which see.
    PIPHER family (East Stroudsburg, Pennsylvania) [6 cards], 1912-1914
    TEETS family (East Stroudsburg, Pennsylvania) [11 cards], 1905-1909
    VAN NOSTRAND family (Port Washington, New York) [15 cards], 1906-1913
  - Holidays (Box 90-91)
    Scope and Contents Note